♪ The Big Bang Theory 9x07 ♪
The Spock Resonance
Original Air Date on November 5, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(sword fight sound effects
on video game)
(Bernadette:)Hey. You got a minute?
(Howard:)Not really.
(Howard:)Visigoths are kind of up my butt
right now.
(Bernadette:)Pause the game, Howard.
“Howard”? Uh-oh.
(Howard:)Make room, Visigoths.
'Sup?
(Bernadette:)We need to talk
about redecorating this place.
(Howard:)Oh, no, not this again.
Look,
(Bernadette:)I get that you grew up here
and you're attached to things
(Sheldon:)looking
a certain way, but...
(Bernadette:)I want this to feel
like my house, too.
(Howard:)Oh, honey, of course
it's your house.
(Howard:)Why else would you
be cleaning it all the time?
(chuckles)
(Bernadette:)All right.
Let's start over.
(Bernadette:)I'm redecorating.
(Bernadette:)The furniture,
the carpeting, the walls.
(Bernadette:)I'm changing everything that
depresses me when I look at it.
(Bernadette:)Try not to be one
of those things.
(Howard:)May I say something?
(Bernadette:)Is it about how I can't have
new wallpaper
(Bernadette:)'cause your dad left when you
were little and your mom died?